Jack Wilkinson

2811 West Street, Unit 207 Ames, Iowa 50014 | 4921 Sumpter Drive Milton, Wisconsin

wilkinsonjthomas@gmail.com

github.com/wilkinsonjthomas

608-322-2284

Attended: Spring 2020

Objective

Results-oriented software developer searching for full-time software engineering position to provide value to the company and expand my own knowledge base. Proven experience with version control and a wide variety software languages and development frameworks.

Education

Iowa State University Expected Graduation: May 2021

- Master of Business Administration
- Bachelor of Science in Computer Engineering with Networking Emphasis

University of Birmingham, United Kingdom

• Study Abroad through the Computer Science Department

Skills

- Proven experience with several programming languages and frameworks including:
 - O JavaScript, Java, C++, Python, REACT, PHP, Nodejs, Graphql, and Android Studio
- Experience working in Agile teams and a variety of distinct team environments o Active member of several sports and clubs throughout High School and College, including: IEEE (2018), Our Town (2018), Varsity Show Choir (2014-2017)

Work Experience

Hy-Vee

Software Engineering Intern

May 2020 – August 2020, May 2021 – August 2021

- o Maintained Hy-Vee's fuel saver & rewards program as a part of a full-time development team
- O Utilized REACT, Node is, and Version Control to add features to the Hy-Vee fuel saver app and website
- o Added new features to several Hy-Vee APIs used internally and on the Hy-Vee website
- o Identified and delegated new tasks and team goals and priorities

Iowa State University

Software Developer

May 2019 – November 2019

- Web development for Iowa State University utilizing PHP, JavaScript, SQL and Zend framework
- Researched potential new development tools and frameworks, including REACT
- o Wrote and revised tutorials for incoming employees to include updated best practices and tools
- o Designed project proposals for the Honors Department and headed new teams built around project delivery

Teaching Assistant: Introduction to Object-Oriented Programming

January 2019 – May 2019

Leadership Activities

• First Year Honors Leader

January 2018 – December 2018

- O Assisted incoming Freshmen with a dapting to honors college community life
- Lead classes of 20 high-performance students by creating lesson plans and guiding discussion
- IEEE Social Media Chair

January 2018 – December 2018